Have you woken up the next day, pounding headache, dry mouth, realized it may have been the amount of drink you had last night?
Well, I'm here to tell you about what is the best vodka to end up without a hangover.
How are you?
My name is Jeff Klein and I'm a vodka connoisseur and bartender here at Beak's Old Florida in St. Petersburg.
Now for me the importance of the best vodka is going to be Absolut.
That's going to be your best vodka for no hangover for many reasons.
One, it's a premium vodka.
So you're not getting any type of impurities in there.
Two, the best way not to get a hangover is to cut out the sugar while you're drinking.
One of the biggest things that leads to hangover is when your mixing your vodka with orange juice, soda, Red Bull, all of those sugars are going to dehydrate you and really that's what lands to your hangover.
The next thing about Absolut is, you could drink a vodka water with Absolut because Absolut has a distinctive, slight sweetness at the very end of it.
So that and water, you still get a little sweetness in your drink without having to mix it with any of those dangerous sugars that are going to laid to you being dehydrated the next day.
So best way to keep drinking all night and not going to hangover the next day, stick with Absolut and stick with it and on water.
My name is Jeff Klein and bartender and vodka connoisseur here at Beak's Old Florida and that is the best vodka for no hangover.